<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Python Starter Blog]]></title><description><![CDATA[A starter blog demonstrating what Gatsby can do.]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.app</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 23:32:54 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[Python Post The First]]></title><description><![CDATA[Python Official Site I guess if you’re reading this post you’re at a point where you decided, “I want to learn how to code.” or “I’m…]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.app/python_post/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.app/python_post/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.python.org/downloads/&quot;&gt;Python Official Site&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;gatsby-highlight&quot; data-language=&quot;javascript&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;language-javascript&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-javascript&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;token function&quot;&gt;print&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;token punctuation&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;token string&quot;&gt;&quot;learn python&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;token punctuation&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I guess if you’re reading this post you’re at a point where you decided, “I want to learn how to code.” or “I’m interested in learning the python programming language. Well, I’m a person just like you, who is also interested in learrning to code and I’ve decided to try to learn python this time. Yes, this time, because I’ve tried to get going with coding MANY times over the last 20 years, but I’ve always (fairly quickly) hit a point where I felt I just wasn’t getting it. So, let’s keep our fingers crossed (when we’re not typing) and give it another go, together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First, I want to say that my goal isn’t to become a full-time coder. I’m already in my mid-50’s in a good job in another part of IT and I don’t want to start all over again in a new role. My goal is to learn enough programming to help me in my current role and to broaden my skill-set to become a more valueable employee.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Second, my philosophy wiwth this blog is going to be take it slow and make sure I understand what I’m doing before moving on to the next step.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OK, I think that’s enough for now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be careful out there.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>